dinnerwithmariah.com 2013-08-28

# Dinner With Mariah

We understand the importance of privacy, and nothing is more important the the privacy of our visitors.

## Privacy Policy

At Dinner With Mariah, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit our network, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

## Cookies

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. For more information please see Google Analyics Privacy Overview.

## Log Files

This site employs log files. These log files record data from visitors to this site. The data gathered is non personal and may include things such as your: internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP) name, entry and exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. This data is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement on the site and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for other uses.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.  
This policy was last modified on 11/7/2012
